planetbollywood.com 2019-05-15

# Planet Bollywood - Latest news, information and reviews of Indian movies, music albums, and film stars

At Planet Bollywood we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online and have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Please take a minute to read this policy so that you understand how we treat your personal information. As we update and expand our services, this policy might change, so please check it out periodically. You can review the most current version of the Privacy Policy at any time at: <http://www.planetbollywood.com/privacy.php>. If you have questions about our privacy policy, please e-mail us at support@indolink.com. If you sign-up to be a Planet Bollywood Member or use any of Planet Bollywood's services, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Service](http://www.planetbollywood.com/terms.php). 

Our goal is to provide you with a robust online experience while safeguarding your privacy. Planet Bollywood collects information online primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use the services provided. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, or other personally identifying information. In addition, we collect information about your use of Planet Bollywood's services as well as your likes/dislikes, interests and preferences from your survey responses and usage information. 

We request this information to provide our strongest value to you - a personalized online experience, so we do everything we can to make Planet Bollywood your preferred online destination, and to provide you the content, products and services that might interest you. 

The following describes how your personal information is treated as you make full use of Planet Bollywood's many offerings either on its own or through one of its strategic partners. Our information gathering and dissemination practices, as described in this policy statement, apply only to Planet Bollywood family of sites, and not to other companies or organization's Web sites to which we link. 

**User's IP Address**  
When a person visits our site, our web server automatically recognizes the IP Address of the visitor. We collect the IP Address of visitors to our site, aggregate information on what pages users access or visit, or user-specific information on what pages users access or visit. 

**Voluntary Information**  
The personal information that you choose to disclose to Planet Bollywood is completely a voluntary act. The only way we know something about you personally is if you tell us about yourself by email or via a feedback form, or register for a member account, or participate in surveys, sweepstakes or contests offered through Planet Bollywood. 

**Partners and Other Sites**  
Some of our services are offered in conjunction with partner companies. In order to provide these services, our partners may ask you for some personal information. Our partners are all upstanding companies that will treat your personal information responsibly. But, since we don't own these companies, we can't speak for them on privacy issues. Promotions, contests and sweepstakes running on Planet Bollywood also may be sponsored by other companies. These companies may choose to collect personal information from you. If you don't want your information collected by these sponsors, you can decide not to participate in the promotion, contest or sweepstakes. You should also be aware that our advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not address the information practices of those Web sites or advertisers. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them and contains information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Planet Bollywood and its partners may use cookies to track user traffic patterns and for the personalization feature. When you register for certain personalized services, Planet Bollywood and its partners may use a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on the sites. Cookies also enable you to enter the sites and use services as a member without having to log on each time. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. 

**Our Promise**  
Planet Bollywood will not sell nor rent any of the personal information you provide without giving you notice and an opportunity to refuse disclosure. We make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy wherever we ask you for personal information. 

We may share only aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers (for example - we may tell an advertiser that "x percent of our audience is between age 25-40"). This is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual person. We do this so that our advertisers understand your needs and tastes better, helping us to keep bringing you first-rate services that might interest you. Moreover, we always give you an option of whether or not you want to receive any information about offers and promotions from us. 

We will take extra precautions in dealing with personal information of registered users under the age of 18. However, these precautions are just a start, and there are some actions we cannot control, where we need help from the child's parent or guardian as well. 

**Mailing List**  
We will occasionally send you emails keeping you updated about changes, new features and special member offers, and various promotions from our partners and sponsors, etc. 

**Opting-Out**  
We offer the users the opportunity to opt-out, terminate the service, or no longer receive future communications from us. Simply send an e-mail to us at: support@indolink.com with appropriate removal instructions. 

**Security**  
Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. If we believe that Planet Bollywood property or an individual's safety or security is at risk, we reserve the right to disclose this information to proper court or law enforcement agencies. 

One last thing to keep in mind -- whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others. If you post personal information in public places, others may send you unsolicited e-mail messages. Always be smart about the information you provide online.
